Ayoub Mouloua

Information Security Analyst

9	29, Hay salam ext 3 sidi said, Meknes, Morocco contact.ayoub0x1@gmail.com +212645469366 https://ayoub0x1.me
	iii 20 Mar 2001 ► Moroccan 🚓 B in ayoub0x1 🗖 ayoub0x1#4552 🗘 ayoub0x1
	ttps://app.hackthebox.com/profile/803489

PROFILE

Skilled Cybersecurity Engineer student with expertise in risk management, unauthorized access, viruses, managing networks, server administration, deploying and monitoring SIEM, and a wide range of vulnerabilities and threats. Well-versed in direct and remote analysis with strong critical thinking, communication, and people skills

EDUCATION

42 Associate degree, 1337Sep 2021 – presentIT training in several fields: Information security, programming, networking...Khouribga, Morocco

English literature, Moulay Ismail University
English Studies as a second major

Baccalaureate, Manfalouti high school

Baccalaureate degree in physics and chemistry

Sep 2016 – Sep 2019

Meknes, Morocco

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Bug Bounty Hunter, HackerOne

Participated in many public and private bug bounty programs through the responsible disclosure of security vulnerabilities in various web technologies and applications to high-profile organizations. Some statistics include but are not limited to:

• Found and Reported several security vulnerabilities and got fixed.

Over 20 acknowledgments were received (U.S. Dept Of Defense, AT&T, IBM, Semrush, Moneybird, Automattic, Hyatt Hotels, etc.).

• Reference: hackerone.com/ayoub0x1

CTF Player | Hacker Ranked, HackTheBox

• Solved many challenges related to OSINT, WEB, REVERSING, MISK

Owns several users and systems by solving some machines related to Linux and Windows

• Reference: https://app.hackthebox.com/profile/803489

Remote

Apr 2020 - present

Sep 2019 - present

Meknes, Morocco

Nov 2021 – present Remote

⟨♥⟩ SKILLS				
Programming C / C++ / Python / Bash	• • • •	Web Penetration Test Manual/Automation Audit, vulnerability assessment	••••	
Networking Routing, Network security	••••	SIEM / SOC Elastic stack, Prometheus	••••	
	© LAN	GUAGES		
Arabic	• • • •	English	••••	
French	• • • • •			

🗐 CERTIFICATES

Introduction to Cybersecurity

Networking Essentials

Cisco